yourather.com 2019-06-06

# Spin Master - Privacy Policy

Effective Date November 2012 (last updated May 2018) 

## This Privacy Policy applies to our sites and apps.

This Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where it is located. This includes our websites like www.zoomerpup.com. It also applies to our mobile sites and apps. By interacting with us, you consent to these practices.

## Our privacy practices and children.

Under the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, you can review your child’s information by contacting us at [customercare@spinmaster.com](mailto:customercare@spinmaster.com). You may also request that we no longer collect information from your child or have your child’s information deleted. To do so, contact us at the email address or phone number below..

## We collect information from and about you and children under 13.

**Children's Information.** We collect what is reasonably necessary for kids to participate on our site. This might include gender and age. This might also include an email address. We may also collect usernames or chat logs.

**Parent and Other Adults’ Information.**

We collect parents’ email addresses. We may collect this from the child or the parent. We may also collect credit card numbers from parents for purchases on our site.

**Information you submit or post.**

We collect information posted in a public space on our site. We also collect information if you or your child contacts us.

**Other information.**

If you or your child uses our website, we may collect information about the browser used or user’s IP address. We might look at what site you or your child came from, or visit next. We may collect passive information about what activity you or the child did or how long the child played.

## We collect information in different ways.

**We collect information directly.** For example, if you or your child create an account with us. We also collect information if you or your child contacts us.

**We collect information passively.** We use [tracking tools](http://www.spinmaster.com/tracking-tools.php) like browser cookies and web beacons to collect information from you.

## We use information as disclosed and described here.

**How we use children’s information.** Unless permitted by law, we use children’s information after getting parental consent. In some circumstances we may not request parental consent. For example, if we are only going to use the information one time to respond to a direct request. Or if we are using information obtained from a child to get parental consent. We also use children’s information as described in any request for parental consent.

**How we use parent and guardian information.** We use email addresses to notify parents or guardians that their children have registered on our site. We may also use your email address to communicate about your child’s account. We may contact you about this Policy or our website Terms.

**We use children and parent’s information to improve our products and services.** We may use information to make our website and products better. We might use information to customize you or your child’s experience with us. For example, we might use information to store your child’s password if he or she registers for our site.

**We use information for security purposes.** We may use information to protect our company, our customers, and our websites. We keep the data that we collect about you for as long as necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

**We use adult’s information for marketing purposes.** For example, we might send adults information about new site features. We might send adults information about third party offers or products we think you might find interesting.

**We use information as otherwise disclosed or permitted by law.** For example, we will use information about children as we describe in parental consent requests.

## We may share information with third parties.

**We may share children’s information.** We will share children’s information if we’re required to by law. We will share it if Spin Master transfers ownership. We will also share children’s information with vendors who help us run our site. We do not currently have any platforms that are designed to let children make their personal information publicly available.

**We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf.** For example, we share information with vendors who help us send emails and operate our sites. We also share information with vendors to complete payments or administer a promotion.

**We may share adult’s information with our business partners.** For example, we might share information with third parties who co-sponsor a promotion. These partners may send adults information about events and products by mail or email.

**We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves.** For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

**We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.** For example, if part of our business was sold we may give our user information as part of that transaction.

**We will share information with other Spin Master entities.**

**We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.**

## You have certain choices about sharing and marketing practices.

**You can opt out of receiving our marketing emails.** To stop receiving our promotional emails, follow the instructions in any promotional message you get from us. Don’t worry! Even if you opt out of getting marketing messages, we will still send you transactional messages. These include responses to your questions, information about your children, or information about your account or your orders.

**You can control if we share information with third parties for their marketing purposes.** To opt out of having us share your information with third parties for their promotional purposes, email us at [hostmaster@spinmasterstudios.com](mailto:hostmaster@spinmasterstudios.com) or call us at 1-800-622-8339.

**You can control cookies and[tracking tools](http://www.spinmaster.com/tracking-tools.php).** Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How you do so depends on the type of cookie. Certain browsers can be set to reject browser cookies. To control flash cookies, which we may use on certain websites from time to time, you can go [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html). Why? Because flash cookies cannot be controlled through your browser settings. If you block cookies or enable your browser’s “do not track” settings, certain features on our sites may not work.

## We use standard security measures.

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. This includes not sharing your passwords. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

Parents, you can take steps to protect your kids too. To learn more about how to protect your child online, read the helpful [information provided by the FTC](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/features/feature-0038-onguardonline). Please also read [this bulletin](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online).

## We store information both in and outside of the United States.

Information we maintain may be stored both within and outside of the United States. Where possible, we try to keep the information you supply to us locally. However, as part of the services offered through our site, the information you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA). By way of example, this may happen where any of our servers are hosted by one of our Spin Master offices outside of the EEA, or one of our service providers is located in a country outside of the EEA. We may also share information between our group companies which are located in countries worldwide. If you require contact details of our other group companies, please contact us. This site is subject to U.S. laws, which may not afford the same level of protection as those in your country. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the EEA. If we transfer your information outside of the EEA in this way, we will take appropriate steps to ensure that any personal data relating to you will continue to be adequately protected.

## We may link to other sites or have third party services on our site we don't control.

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This includes social media sites. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of these websites. Read the privacy policy of other websites and insurance carriers carefully. We are not responsible for these third party practices.

## Feel free to contact us if you have more questions.

If you have any questions about this Policy or our processing of data about you, please contact us at [dpo@spinmaster.com](mailto:dpo@spinmaster.com).

Or via mail at: 

> Data Protection Officer  
>  225 King Street West  
>  Toronto, ON M5V 3M2  
> 

If you have a concern about our handling of your personal information, please get in contact with us first so we can try to resolve your query. If however you feel we have not dealt with your concern and that we are failing to meet our legal obligations, you can report this to your local data protection regulator. 

## We may update this Policy.

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.

© 2019 Spin Master Ltd. All rights reserved.
